[
    {
        "question": "Lata said to me, \"Where do you live ?\"",
        "words": {
          "4": "I",
          "1": "me",
          "3": "Lata",
          "2": "where",
          "5": "did",
          "6": "to",
          "7": "asked",
          "8": "lived",
          "9": "that"
        },
        "answers":[[3,7,1,2,4,8]]
    },
    {
        "question": "She said, \"What are you doing ?\"",
        "words": {
          "4": "she",
          "1": "I",
          "3": "me",
          "2": "was",
          "5": "to",
          "6": "what",
          "7": "that",
          "8": "doing",
          "9": "asked",
          "10": "am"
        },
        "answers":[[4,9,3,6,1,2,8]]
    },
    {
        "question": "The thief says to me, \"How have I come here ?\"",
        "words": {
          "4": "thief",
          "1": "come",
          "3": "he",
          "2": "the",
          "5": "me",
          "6": "had",
          "7": "how",
          "8": "that",
          "9": "asks",
          "10": "has",
          "11": "here",
          "12": "to"
        },
        "answers":[[2,4,9,5,7,3,10,1,11]]
    },
    {
        "question": "The thief said to me, \"How have I come here ?\"",
        "words": {
          "4": "thief",
          "1": "come",
          "3": "he",
          "2": "the",
          "5": "me",
          "6": "had",
          "7": "how",
          "8": "that",
          "9": "asks",
          "10": "has",
          "11": "here",
          "12": "to"
        },
        "answers":[[2,4,9,5,7,3,6,1,11]]
    },
    {
        "question": "The student told the teacher, \"When can I come to you ?\"",
        "words": {
          "4": "the teacher",
          "1": "asked",
          "3": "come",
          "2": "he",
          "5": "The student",
          "6": "to",
          "7": "when",
          "8": "could",
          "9": "him",
          "10": "the student",
          "11": "that"
        },
        "answers":[[5,1,4,7,10,8,3,6,9],[10,1,4,7,5,8,3,6,9]]
    },
    {
        "question": "The teacher said, \"Who was this great man ?\"",
        "words": {
          "4": "this",
          "1": "the",
          "3": "had",
          "2": "that",
          "5": "teacher",
          "6": "who",
          "7": "great",
          "8": "asked",
          "9": "been",
          "10": "man"
        },
        "answers":[[1,5,8,6,2,7,10,3,9]]
    },
    {
        "question": "The judge told the killer, \"Why did you kill your wife ?\"",
        "words": {
          "4": "the killer",
          "1": "been",
          "3": "why",
          "2": "the judge",
          "5": "he",
          "6": "his",
          "7": "had",
          "8": "asked",
          "9": "wife",
          "10": "why",
          "11": "killed"
        },
        "answers":[[2,8,4,3,5,7,11,6,9]]
    },
    {
        "question": "The judge said to the killer, \"How was your wife killed ?\"",
        "words": {
          "4": "the killer",
          "1": "been",
          "3": "how",
          "2": "the judge",
          "5": "he",
          "6": "his",
          "7": "had",
          "8": "asked",
          "9": "wife",
          "10": "why",
          "11": "killed"
        },
        "answers":[[2,8,4,3,6,9,7,1,11]]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sangeeta cried, \"How shall I pass the examination then ?\"",
        "words": {
          "4": "cried",
          "1": "examination",
          "3": "how",
          "2": "that",
          "5": "the",
          "6": "she",
          "7": "Sangeeta",
          "8": "case",
          "9": "now",
          "10": "in",
          "11": "asked",
          "12": "pass",
          "13": "case",
          "14": "and",
          "15": "would"
        },
        "answers":[[7,4,14,11,3,6,15,12,5,1,10,2,13]]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alok told Nomita, \"Do you love me ?\"",
        "words": {
          "4": "Nomita",
          "1": "loved",
          "3": "Alok",
          "2": "that",
          "5": "she",
          "6": "him",
          "7": "if",
          "8": "asked"
        },
        "answers":[[3,8,4,7,5,1,6]]
    },
    {
        "question": "Nabin said, \"Are you living here ?\"",
        "words": {
          "4": "Nabin",
          "1": "whether",
          "3": "I",
          "2": "there",
          "5": "me",
          "6": "been",
          "7": "was",
          "8": "asked",
          "9": "living"
        },
        "answers":[[4,8,5,1,3,7,9,2]]
    },
    {
        "question": "She asked me, \"Have you ever been to England ?\"",
        "words": {
          "4": "England",
          "1": "had",
          "3": "me",
          "2": "I",
          "5": "she",
          "6": "to",
          "7": "if",
          "8": "ever",
          "9": "was",
          "10": "been",
          "11": "asked",
          "12": "that"
        },
        "answers":[[5,11,3,7,2,1,8,10,6,4]]
    }
]